Finding Aid for Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project Records, 1947-2003
Bentley Historical Library
- Prospects
  - Parker, George E. Jr., 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - Parker Rust Proof Company, 1951-1960 (Box 27)
  - Paul, Robert, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Peet, Charles D., 1960-1965 (Box 27)
  - Peninsular Slate Company, 1960-1964 (Box 27)
  - Pennell, Frank W., 1960 (Box 27)
  - People's National Bank, 1961-1964 (Box 27)
  - People to People, 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - Perkins, Richard, 1961-1967 (Box 27)
  - Perring, Raymond T., 1960-1963 (Box 27)
  - Pet Milk Company, 1961 (Box 27)
  - Pettibone, Charles L., 1959 (Box 27)
  - Pfeiffer Brewing Company, 1952-1964 (Box 27)
  - Philadelphia Electric Company, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Pinkus, Hermann, M.D., 1960 (Box 27)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, 1950-1953 (Box 27)
  - Pontiac Press, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Pontiums, Miller H., 1959-1960 (Box 27)
  - Poorman, William F., 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - Procter & Gamble Company, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Pure Oil Company Foundation, 1960-1963 (Box 27)
  - Pryor, Thomas & Esther Foundation, 1960 (Box 27)
  - "R" Miscellaneous, 1960-1972 (Box 27)
  - Reichhold Chemicals Incorporated, 1953-1960 (Box 27)
  - Reo Holding Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 27)
  - Reynolds Metals Company, 1954-1964 (Box 27)
  - Robbins, Hunter S., 1959-1963 (Box 27)
  - Roberts, Robert, 1960-1968 (Box 27)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1960-1967 (Box 27)
  - Rosenbaum, Lester F., 1961-1964 (Box 27)
  - Rosenthal, Morton L., 1961-1964 (Box 27)
  - Ruthven, Dr. Alexander G., 1959-1969 (Box 27)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Sackett, Samuel J., 1959-1966 (Box 27)
  - Sackett, Ray C., 1959-1961 (Box 27)
  - Saums Honorary Degree, 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - Sawyer, Dr. Ralph A., 1959-1962 (Box 27)
  - Seabury Foundation, 1962-1966 (Box 27)
  - Seabury, C. Ward, 1959-1960 (Box 27)
  - Sealed Power Corporation, 1961-1964 (Box 27)
  - Sears Roebuck Co., 1960-1965 (Box 27)
  - Shell Oil Company, 1959-1960 (Box 27)
  - Sherwood, B.P., 1959-1963 (Box 27)
  - Sloan Foundation, 1959-1964 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Eberle M., 1959-1964 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Fred, 1947-1965 (Box 27)
  - Socony-Vacum Oil Company, 1951-1960 (Box 27)
  - Square D. Company, 1951-1960 (Box 27)
  - Staebler, Neil, 1960-1964 (Box 27)
  - Stalker Corp., 1960-1964 (Box 27)
  - Stearns, Russell B., 1959-1960 (Box 27)
  - Steelcase, 1959-1960 (Box 27)
  - Stranahan, Robert A. and Foundation, 1960-1964 (Box 27)
  - Studebaker Packard, 1951-1960 (Box 27)
  - Sun Life Insurance Co., 1960 (Box 27)
  - Sutherland Paper Co., 1951-1959 (Box 27)
  - "T" Miscellaneous, 1960-1971 (Box 27)
  - Talbot, Cyril, 1959-1962 (Box 27)
  - Tecumseh Products Company, 1950-1962 (Box 27)
  - Texas Room, 1961-1966 (Box 27)
  - Thompson Ramo Woolridge Corporation, 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - Timken Roller Bearing Company, 1950-1954 (Box 27)
  - Toledo Scale Company, 1960-1962 (Box 27)
  - Toledo Trust Company, 1960-1964 (Box 27)
  - Townsend and Bottum, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - Towsley, Dr. and Mrs. Harry A., 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Udylite Corporation, 1951-1960 (Box 27)
  - Unger Foundation, Inc., 1960 (Box 27)
  - United States Rubber Company, 1951-1961 (Box 27)
  - University of Michigan Club of Buffalo, 1960-1961 (Box 27)
  - Upjohn, 1951-1982 (Box 27)
  - "V" Miscellaneous, 1960-1982 (Box 27)
  - Van Domelen, Peter, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Visking Corporation, 1953 (Box 27)
  - "W" Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Wagner, Harvey A., 1959-1963 (Box 27)
  - Walgreen, Charles R., 1959-1964
  - Walter, Erich A., 1959-1961 (Box 27)
  - Walton, C.W., Minnesota Mining & Mfg. Co., 1961 (Box 27)
  - Warrick, Woodward A., 1959-1964 (Box 27)
  - Watkins, James K., 1959-1962 (Box 27)
  - Watling, Lerchen & Co., 1961 (Box 27)
  - Webber, Oscar, 1959-1961 (Box 27)
  - Weber, Alvin H., 1959-1964 (Box 27)
  - Welch, Robert A. Foundation, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Wetterau, G.E., 1960 (Box 27)
  - Wheat, Renville, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Whirlpool Division of RCA, 1951-1964 (Box 27)
  - Wickes Corporation, 1951-1960 (Box 27)
  - Wickes, Harvey R., 1959-1964 (Box 27)
  - Williams, Gov. G. Mennen, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Wilison, Mrs. George C., 1959-1963 (Box 27)
  - Willys Motors, Inc., 1951-1962 (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Steven, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Charles E., 1959 (Box 27)
  - Winkelman, Stuart H., 1962-1967 (Box 27)
  - Woodall Industries, 1951-1964 (Box 27)
  - Wright Air Development Proposal, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Wright, Edward, 1959-1961 (Box 27)
  - Wyandotte Chemicals Corp., 1952-1965 (Box 27)
  - "XYZ" Miscellaneous, 1960-1989 (Box 27)
  - Yoder, Jonathan S., 1959-1960 (Box 27)
  - Young Helpers of Detroit, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Zeder, James C., 1959-1968 (Box 27)
  - Ziv, Frederic W., 1959-1960 (Box 27)
- Donors
  The Donors series, 1948-1996 (3 linear ft.), includes two types of records: the Master Set of Donor Cards and the Memorial Volumes. The Master Set of Donor Cards is comprised of cards and copies of transactions for each donor, corporate and individual through 1996. The cards are arranged alphabetically and are housed in four .5 linear feet boxes. The Memorial Volumes are an undated set of seven bound books. At the time they were prepared (unfortunately unknown, but estimated to be in the late 1960s or early 1970s), they contained a complete list of individual (non-corporate) contributors.
  The first volume contains the names of the National Board of Officers and Sponsors, followed by a list of individual donors and the person memorialized. The next six volumes include an alphabetically arranged list of names. According to a document in the History series (Box 4, History, Background Material, Memorial Volumes in George Mason Library), the volumes were compiled from an IBM list of donors once kept in the Rackham office, title pages to each volume were hand lettered, illustrative material was prepared by Dwight Gadbery, and the list was typed by Edna Robbins on a "special IBM typewriter in 400 typing hours." The volumes were bound by the university bindery and kept in a case especially designed for them in the Phoenix library entitled "Honor Roll of Donors to the Michigan Memorial-Phoenix Project." Researchers should note that contributors who gave money toward cancer research were listed in a companion volume identically bound and kept in the Alice Crocker Lloyd Therapy Center. The record group does not include the Crocker volume.
  - Donor File cards, 1948-1996
    - A-D (Box 28)
    - E-K (Box 29)
    - L-R (Box 30)
    - S-Z (Box 31)
  - Memorial Volumes I-VII, undated (Box 32)
- Research, 1948-2003
  Collectively, the Research series, 1948-2003 (20.5 linear ft.), offers a precise and detailed view of Phoenix supported research. Records exist for all but one (# 802) of 816 funded projects, which are arranged chronologically by grant number. Included for most are the initial grant request, progress reports, and a final summary of the project's accomplishments. Frequently there are substantial final reports in the file, publications resulting from the project, and bibliographies. The series also includes a run of applications for funds arranged by year, 1948-1961; a run of applications arranged by year with accompanying evaluations and comments, 1968-1994; and a set of index cards. The index cards are arranged alphabetically by project director and include the name of the project, the amount funded, and opening and closing dates. Researchers are reminded that there is also a series comprised of early research material in the first accession. The Research series also includes a compendium of research grants funded by the Phoenix Project since the inception of the grant award process in 1948. Additional information regarding the grant-decision making process and project evaluations can be found in the Faculty Executive Committee files in the Minutes of Meetings series.
  - Administrative (Box 33)
    - Application Lists and Summaries, 1968-1994; 13 folders (Box 33)
    - Project Directors, circa 1948-1996 (Box 33)
    - Research Funds, 1948-1961; 11 folders (Box 34)
    - Research Rejects, Fall 1981 (Box 34)
    - Research Projects Restricted, 1952-1955 (Box 34)
    - Seed Funding Program, 2018; 1 folder (Box 34)
  - Research Grants, Nos. 1-816, 1948-1996
    - #1-#200
      - Radioactive Iodine Research, W. H. Beierwaltes, [1.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Chromosome Investigations Using Phosphorus 32, R.J. Lowry and R.C. Williams, [2.] (Box 35)
      - Tracer Studies on the Dakin-West Reaction, C.S. Rondestvedt, Jr., [3.] (Box 35)
      - Mechanism of Rowe Rearrangement, W.R. Vaughn, [4.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Lecturers and Fellowships, F. Miller, [5.] (Box 35)
      - Radiocarbon dating of thirty samples, H.R. Crane and J.B. Griffin, [6.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Isotope Laboratory, F.J. Hodges, [7.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Study of Penetration of 2, 4-Dichlorophenoxyacedtic Acid (Weed Killer) into Plants, F.J. Gustafson, [8.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Post-Glacial Chronology of Aleutians, H.H. Bartlett, [9.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Decarbocylation of 2.3-Dioxypyrrolidines, W. R. Vaughn, [10.] (Box 35)
      - Study of High Energy Cosmic Rays, D.A. Glaser, [11.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Congress and Atomic Energy: A Study in Congressional Direction and Control, J.W. Lederle, [12.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Ion Exchange Resins in the Study of Complex Compounds, R.W. Parry, [13.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Study of Decay of Rubidium, M.L. Wiedenbeck, [14.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Seminar on Public Policy and Atomic Energy, J.K. Pollock, [15.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Oak Ridge Institute Attendance, Melvin Levine, [16.] (Box 35)
      - Polarized X-ray Experiments, P.V.C. Hough, [17.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Synthesis & Utilization of Yolk in Oocytes & Embryos, N.E. Kemp, [18.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Botany, C.D. LaRue, [19.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Effects of Radiation on Bacterial Metabolism, C.A. Lawrence, [20.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Radiation Biophysics--High Energy Particles, C. Levinthal, [21.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Biological and Embryological Processes involved in the Formation of Melanin Pigment in Mamalian Hair, C.L. Markert, [22.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Study of Diffusion of Gases at High Pressure; 1952, 1954 bound reports, J.J. Martin, [23.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Radiochemical Analysis & Nuclear Chemical Separations, W.W. Meinke, [24.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Use of Radioactive Isotopes for Determining the Course of Migration of Larval Lungworms in Deer, E.C. O'Roke, [25.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - U.S. Atomic Energy Commission Field Trip, R.A. Tybout, [26.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Pollen Atlas, S.A. Cain, [27.]; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Protective Coatings on Metal, L.L. Carrick and W.P. Anderson, [28.]; 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Growth of Aspen Trees in the Northern Part of the Lower Peninsula, S.A. Graham, [29.] (Box 36)
      - Legal Problems Arising from Peacetime Uses of Atomic Energy, E.B. Stason, [30.]; 6 folders (Box 36)
      - Impact of Atomic Energy on the American Public, Angus Campbell, [31.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Plant Nutrition Research, K.L. Jones, [32.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Study Aimed at Improving Methods for Evaluating Candidates for the Medical School, E.L. Kelly, [33.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Isotope Research, M. Nickerson, [34.] (Box 36)
      - Study of Carbon-Carbon Bond Cleavage Under Mild Conditions with the Help of Radio Carbon, R.C. Elderfield, [35.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Addition of a Research Leader in Nuclear Physics, E. F. Barker, [36.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Study of Entrance of Radioactive Cobalt into Plants through their Leaves & Its Subsequent Distribution throughout the Plant, F.G. Gustafson, [37.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Antigenic Configuration of Tumor Cell Surfaces, W.J. Nungester, [38.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Support of Cyclotron Research Program, W.C. Parkinson, [39.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Alice Crocker Lloyd Memorial Center, A.C. Furstenberg, [40.]; 2 folders (Box 36)
      - Food Preservation by Radiation from Radioactive Isotopes, L.E. Brownell, [41.]; 2 folders, 1 folder (Box 36)
      - Study of Changes Affecting Useful Life & Effectiveness of School Buildings, W.I. Bennett, [42.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Research Work in Problems Involving Rubber, L.M. Hobbs, [43.]; 3 folders (Box 37)
      - Study of a Method for Clinical Localization of Tumors Using Radioactive Isotope Tracers, E.A. Kahn, W.R. Correa, R.G. Farris, [44.] (Box 37)
      - Normal and Neoplastic Growth and Distribution of Non-protein Nitrogenous Compounds, J.F. Hogg, [45.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Hypertension Research, F. Shideman, [46.] (Box 37)
      - Fate and Mechanism of Action of Carbon Tagged Adrenergic Blocking Agent, M. Nickerson, R.N. Horowitz, [47.] (Box 37)
      - Public Administration Aspects of Atomic Energy Program, F. Heady, [48.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Effect of Irradiation of Rabbits with Brown-Pearch Carcinoma on Universal Reaction, Reuben Kahn, [49.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Immunology of Human Tumors, W.J. Nungester, [50.] (Box 37)
      - Labeled Antibodies Against Cancer, W.H. Beierwaltes, [51.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Synthesis of 6-Substituted N-Methylnipecotic Acids, P.E. Norris, [52.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Basic Research in Structure of Glass, R.L. Hess, [53.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Radiation Control of Food-Borne Parasitic Diseases, S.E. Gould and H.J. Gomberg, [54.]; 6 folders (Box 37)
      - Investigation of Rheumatic Diseases Using Isotope Technique, W.D. Robinson, J.H. Gonyea, [55.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Physical-Chemical Basis of Cell Differentiation, C.L. Markert, [56.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Role of Pituitary Hormones in Protection Against Radiation Damage, R.L. Baker, [57.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Examination of Radioactive Mineral Deposits, E.W. Heinrich, [58.]; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Radiation Biophysics, C. Levinthal and E.S. Lennox, [59.] (Box 38)
      - Lattice Heat Capacities of a Tetrafluoride Series, E. F. Westrum, [60.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - New Methods of Detecting Ionizing Radiation by its Effect on Phase Changes, D.A. Glaser, [61.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Dating of Diastrophism, Vulcanism and Sedimentation in Northern Mexico, L.B. Kellum, [62.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Alice Crocker Lloyd Radiation Therapy Center, F.J. Hodges, [63.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Equipment for Hypertension Research Laboratory, S.W. Hoobler, [64.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Cross-Cultural Study of Urban Patterns, with Special Reference to Factors Affecting Their Reconstruction After Bomb Damage, A.H. Hawley, [65.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Effect of Radiation on Jet Engine Performance, E.T. Vincent, R.B. Morrison & R. Cullen, [66.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Effect of Radiation on Reciprocating Engines Performance, E.T. Vincent and G.J. Van Wylen, [67.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Study of the Iridium Isotopes Formed by the (d,c) Reaction on Platinum, W.W. Meinke, [68.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - The Effects of Gamma Radiation Sterilization on Certain Injectable Pharmaceuticals, W.E. McConnell, [69.] (Box 38)
      - Metabolism of Amino Acids & Related Compounds by Brucellae: the Role of Cellular Permeability, P. Gerhardt, [70.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - The Effect of Gamma Radiation on Plant Tissues in Culture, C.D. La Rue, [71.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Identification of Sensory Receptors in Clagocera, F.E. Smith and E.R. Baylor, [72.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Use of Tetrahymena in Evaluating Effects of Gamma Radiation on Vitamins & Essential Amino Acids, A.M. Elliott and L.E. Brownell, [73.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Sterilization of Tissue Culture Fluids with Gamma Radiation from Cobolt-60, D.J. Merchant, [74.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Ford Reactor Construction, R.B. Mesler, [75.] (Box 38)
      - Development of Improved Techniques for Determination of Neutron Activation Cross Sections, W.W. Meinke, [76.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Accelerator Design Studies, K.N. Terwilliger and L.W. Jones, [77.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Mass Spectrometric Studies of Isotopic Reactions, R.B. Bernstein, [78.] (Box 38)
      - Study of Gas Metal Systems, M.J. Sinnott, [79.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Calculation of the Coulomb Effect in (d,p) Reactions, P.V.C. Hough, [80.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Nickel-Nickel Boundary Diffusion, M.J. Sinnott, [81.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Diffusion in the Iron-Nickel System, M.J. Sinnott, [82.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Microstructure of Sulphur-Containing Iron Alloys, L.H. Van Vlack, [83.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Construction of Multi-Channel Discriminator & Investigation of Nuclear Decay Processes with Newly-Developed Energy Summing Techniques, M.L. Wiedenbeck, [84.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Study of Factors Controlling Enzyme Synthesis, H.O. Halvorson, [85.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Localization of Tetanus Toxin in Rabbits, R.W. Buxton and A.B. Vial, [86.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Study of Distribution of Radioactive Calcium in Human Teeth When Utilized as Ca-45 Hydroxide Applied Topically to Remaining Portions of Amputated Pulpal Tissue, J.T. Hartsook, [87.]; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Effect of Alpha Radiation on Combustion, R.B. Morrison, [88.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Effect of Radiation on Constant Volume Combustion Processes, G.J. Van Wylen, [89.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Radioactive Dust, R.C. Porter, [90.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Inactivation of Viruses with Gamma Radiation from Cobalt-60, L.L. Kempe and F. Whitehouse, [91.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Effects of chronic irradiation on bacterial cultures under conditions of continuous growth, D.L. Nanney, [92.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Study on Temperature Embrittlement in Steel, C.A. Siebert, [93.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Study of Evaporator for Concentrating Radioactive Solutions, L.E. Brownell, [94.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Study of Use of Antimony-Beryllium Sources in Activation Analysis, W.W. Meinke, [95.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Iron Metabolism & Erythrocyte Survival in Refractory Anemias, R.C. Bishop, [96.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Effect on normal brain and cranial nerves of radioactive substances, R.C. Schneider, [97.] (Box 39)
      - Effect of Gamma Radiation on Chemical Reactions, L.C. Anderson, [98.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Iodine-131 Treatment of Pulmonary Emphysema, W.H. Beierwaltes, [99.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Radioactive Chromate Determination of Blood Volume, R.J. Bolt, [100.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Distribution and Fate of Labeled Drugs, M.H. Seevers, [101.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - A Television Nuclear Emulsion Scanner, P.V.C. Hough, [102.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - The Preparation of Certain C14 Labeled Bicyclic Terpenes, W.R. Vaughan, [103.] (Box 39)
      - Use of Antitumor Antibodies of High Radioactivity, P.C. Rajam, [104.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Capillary Permeability Following X-radiation and Gamma Radiation from Cobolt-60, F. Whitehouse, [105.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Occupational Choice among Nuclear Scientists, H.L. Wilensky, [106.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - International Implications of Atomic Power for American Foreign Policy, D. Wit, [107.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Effects of Gamma Radiation on Cyanide, Sulfide, and Phenol Waste, G.M. Ridenour, [108.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Ford Agricultural Plant Nutrition Project, A.G. Norman, [109.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, H.J. Gomberg, [110.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Histologic Study of Bone Grafts Comparing Cobalt Irradiated Grafts to Those Sterilized by Other Means, D.S. Maxwell, [111.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Biosynthesis of Ribose in Microorganisms and Animals, In Vivo, I.A. Bernstein, [112.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Isotopic Exchange Reactions involving Fluorine-18; Stability of Group V Fluorides, R.B. Bernstein and R.W. Parry, [113.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - A comparison of lake types by primary productivity measurements, G.H. Lauff, [114.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Investigation of Location of Heavy Metals on cell Surface Using Radioactive Isotopes, R.J. Lowry and A.S. Sussman, [115.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Synthesis of C-14 Labeled Analgesics & Extraction from Biological Material, L.A. Woods, [116.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Metabolic Utilization of Parenteral Sodium Administered During States of Sodium Depletion, R.E.L. Berry, [117.]; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Molecular Autoradiography of Nucleic Acids, C. Levinthal, [118.] (Box 40)
      - Thermodynamics of Solutes in Liquid Uranium, D.V. Ragone, [119.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Effect of Neutron & Gamma Radiation Chemical Reactions, J.J. Martin, [120.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Activation Analysis with Michigan Ford Reactor, W.W. Meinke, [121.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Identification & Synthesis of Activated Carbon Dioxide, M.J. Coon, [122.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Permeability of Bacterial Spores, P. Gerhardt, [123.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Studies on Adjuvant Effect & Bacterial Endotoxins on Antibody Production, A.G. Johnson, [124]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Archaeological Survey of the Upper Peninsula, Michigan, A.C. Spaulding, [125.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Metabolism of Dihydroxyacetone in Normal & Diabetic Animal, G.H. Lowrey and M.U. Tsao, [126.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Effect of Radiation on Daphnia Population Growth, L.B. Slobodkin, [127.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Chemical Disruption of Dormancy in Neurospora, A.S. Sussman, [128.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Evaluation of Metabolic Pathways in Microorganisms, H.J. Blumenthal, [129.] (Box 40)
      - Machine Scanning of Nuclear Emulsions, P.V.C. Hough, [130.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Biosynthesis of Long Chain Aldehyde (s), W.E.M. Lands, [131.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Study of Radioactivity Levels in Prehistoric Materials, F.P. Thieme, [132.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Effects of Carnitine on Metabolic Processes, I.B. Fritz, [133.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Equipping of Isotope Laboratory in Virus Laboratory, T. Francis, [134.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Effect of Reactor Radiation on Chemical Reactions, L.C. Anderson, [135.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Protein turnover during germination in Neurospora ascospores, A.S. Sussman, [136.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Biosynthesis of Pyridoxal, W.G. Robinson, [137.] (Box 40)
      - Preparation of Radioactive Antibodies by Recoil-Exchange in the Nuclear Reaction, P.C. Rajam, [138.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Experimental Production of Solitary Bone Cysts as a Method of Studying the Etiology Metaphyseal Bone Cysts, C.E. Badgley, [139.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Changes in Electrolyte Metabolism Resulting from Adrenocortical Steroids..., J.W. Conn, [140.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - An Investigation of Phenanthryltetrazoles, P.A.S. Smith, [141.] (Box 40)
      - Effect of Gamma Radiation on Aluminus Catalysts, L.C. Anderson, [142.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Healing of Anorganic Bone and Tooth Grafts, J.K. Avery, [143.] (Box 40)
      - Studies on the Mechanism of Formation of the Ergot Alkaloids, A.G. Paul, [144.] (Box 40)
      - Early Modification of Cellular Ultra-Structure after Irradiation, B.L. Baker, [145.] (Box 40)
      - Liquid Scintillation Spectrometer, R.A. Sawyer, [146.] (Box 40)
      - 40 Mev Deuteron Cyclotron, W.C. Parkinson, [147.] (Box 40)
      - Life Span of Human Epidermal Cells, R.O. Dingman, [148.] (Box 40)
      - Medical Application of Calcium 47, D.R. Korst, [149.] (Box 40)
      - Investigation of Rare Earth Thorium Mineral Deposits, E.W. Heinrich, [150.] (Box 40)